<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brunch on Pastel Cravings</title>
    <link>http://pastelcravings.ca/tags/brunch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brunch on Pastel Cravings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:02:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://pastelcravings.ca/tags/brunch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Régine Café</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/reginecafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:02:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/reginecafe/</guid>
      <description>Regine Cafe   The Gaufré This place is by far, my favorite brunch spot for numerous reasons. First of all, the menu offers many interesting and creative choices, such as Scottish eggs, brioche bread, pulled ham, trout gravlax and mascarpone cheese cream. Even their oatmeal, made with coconut milk and mango jam, tastes spectacular. Every bite is heaven and the presentation is gorgeous. For those who are gluten intolerance, they offer a few gluten-free options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Café Melbourne</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/cafemelbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 20:01:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/cafemelbourne/</guid>
      <description>As you enter The Mile End, one of the hippest areas in Montreal, you’ll come across a quaint little brunch spot called Le Café Melbourne. First, you’ll notice a sign reading &amp;ldquo;Our French is not good, but our coffee is”, flash a grin, enter the café, and be greeted with the warm smiles of the Australian owner and his staff. Take a seat, and get ready for some Insta-worthy moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to Study</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/topstudycafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 20:02:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.ca/post/topstudycafe/</guid>
      <description>For this special post, I’ve asked my co-bloggers to list me all their top coffee places to study and I’ve assembled the ones that was in common on our lists.
Legend: &amp;hearts; = the bloggers’ favourites
1. La Finca Coffee &amp;amp; Office | &amp;hearts; Laura
| &amp;hearts; Trang
| ADDRESS: 1067 Rue de Bleury, Montréal, QC H2Z 1N1 | Métro Place D’Armes
La Finca   A favourite of mine because of the accessibility by metro, the coziness of the place and the instagrammy worth of everyshot and every angle!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>