<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Downtown Montreal on Pastel Cravings</title>
    <link>http://pastelcravings.com/tags/downtown-montreal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Downtown Montreal on Pastel Cravings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:06:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://pastelcravings.com/tags/downtown-montreal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kumamoto Ramen</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.com/post/kumamoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:06:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.com/post/kumamoto/</guid>
      <description>When I heard about this new ramen place in town, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier. Because more ramen is always good.
What&amp;rsquo;s cool about this new restaurant is the isolation booth concept. You have these wood panels separating you and you neighbors. You have a little button for ordering food and an autorefill water system.Then you receive your bowl of ramen through a curtain covered window.
Unique Ramen I ordered a Black Tonkotsu Ramen and it was so savoury and delicious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Spoon</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.com/post/cafespoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 10:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.com/post/cafespoon/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I&amp;rsquo;m at Guy Concordia or Peel and I (a petit poussin) find myself searching for a coffee shop, this one is the first to pop in my head. Very accessible by metro, it only took me 5 mins to walk to Crescent St and find this little jewel. I love the decor, immediately the combination of the green from the plants and the white modern look caught my eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kampai Garden</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.com/post/kampaigarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 11:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.com/post/kampaigarden/</guid>
      <description>Kampai Garden was one the most popular place even before it opened its doors last summer. Why? Because everything in the restaurant screams Instagram! From neon lights in the wall, to the french sentence, to the plants giving that green vibe everywhere.
Kampai Logo  Kampai Food     Kampai menu is very unique. I went there for supper the first time, got me some beef sashimi, sweet potato fries and fried chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizzeria No.900</title>
      <link>http://pastelcravings.com/post/pizza900/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 10:24:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pastelcravings.com/post/pizza900/</guid>
      <description>Once you enter the place, you will notice the coziness of the entrance. However, it’s only an illusion since they have more seats behind.
Comptoir  Comptoir     I ordered a Margherita Pizza (9$) and my boyfriend got the Italian Sausage (13$). The crust was perfect, not too dry, a little chewy and soft in the center. Tomato sauce was okay but what really amazes me was … THE CHEESE, miam!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>